Burd-Shippen Papers 1708-1792 Mss.B.B892
American Philosophical Society
- Legal and Financial, 1708-1791, Undated; Series II
  - Reports on the workmen on the road [cutting the road to Ohio], 1757 January 6 - November 21; 27pp. (Box 5)
    List giving number of men working at particular sites on given date.
  - Statement that the account of Frederick Berzone against Lewis Mororo is correct ..., 1757 February 2; 1p.; Forster, Thomas (Box 5)
    Verification of account.
  - Affidavit concerning debt between Robert Chittock and William Ellis, 1757 May 9; 1p.; Ellis, William (Box 5)
    Affidavit of debt.
  - Account with the estate of Lewis Murrow, 1757 May 10; 1p.; Clark, Daniel (Box 5)
  - Oath of certain persons being indebted to him..., 1757 May 14; 1p.; Dougherty, Dudley (Box 5)
    Signed oath.
  - Order to James Burd to Pay William Rodman £4, 1757 May 14; 1p.; Bard, John (Box 5)
    Payment order.
  - Order to pay Dudley Dougherty from Rodman's pay., 1757 May 15; 1p.; Rodman, Michael (Box 5)
  - Certification of James Crampton, 1757 July 15; 1p.; Elder, John and James Galbreath (Box 5)
    Certificaion of employment with the Province.
  - Promissory note to Joseph Falkner, 1757 July 21; 1p.; Kelley, Joseph (Box 5)
    Promise to pay debt.
  - Robert Roach account with Dudley Dougherty, 1757 September 12; 1p. (Box 5)
    Listing of money owed.
  - Memorandum of money for James Burd, 1757 September 21; 1p.; Burd, Sarah Shippen, 1731-1784 (Box 5)
    Listing of money to be paid.
  - Statement of wines and rum sold to "Conelon Burd", 1757 December 20; 1p. (Box 5)
    Invoice for cost and amount sold.
  - Account of Leonard Ellis for shoes, etc. ..., 1757 - 1763; 1p.; Bowsman, Henry (Box 5)
    Invoice of items sold.
  - Statement of accounts of James Pemberton ..., 1758 November 7; 1p.; Burd, James (Box 5)
    Account for bearskins.
  - Statement of accounts for linen, etc., 1759 July 5; 1p.; Catringer (Box 5)
    List of items and cost.
  - Power of attorney, 1759 July 6; 1p.; Gillespie, Allen and Hugh Swan (Box 5)
    Makes James Burd their attorney.
  - Account sheet, 1761 April 22; Burd, James (Drawer Oversize)
    General note
    Autographed document signed 4 pages
  - Advertisement of a strayed or stolen mare, 1761 October 3; 1p.; Shippen, Edward (Box 5)
    Lancaster. Describes mare.
  - Return of beef cattle..., 1761 October 11; 1p.; Durock, James (Box 5)
    Gives return by cattle at grass and to be slaughtered.
  - Account of James Burd for linnen, etc., 1761 December 10; 1p.; Shippen, Joseph Jr. (Box 5)
    Philadelphia. Gives description of item, length, and amount.
  - Sundry's bought by James Burd, 1761; 1p. (Box 5)
    Pittsburgh. Lists number of items.
  - Statement of account for oats, hay..., 1762; 1p.; Frazer, John (Box 5)
    Lists number of items and cost.
  - Statement of account to John Adams for whip, rum..., 1762-1764; 1p.; Fulton, Robert (Box 5)
  - Invoice of sundry goods ... shoes, threads, etc. purchased..., 1763 February 1; 1p. (Box 5)
    Lists number of items, and value.
  - Claim against John Beaver for £7, 1763 October 14; 2pp.; Steiner, Christian (Box 5)
    Lists claims and amounts paid.
  - Account with James McGinis, 1764 February - April; 1p.; Frey, George (Box 5)
    By date, lists items purchased, and amount.
  - Book as constable in Lancaster County, 1764; 20pp.; Burd, James (Box 5)
    Gives a summary of various actions performed as constable, and a list of fees.
  - Certification of freedom of George Chelcott, 1764 June 12; 1p.; Wright, James (Box 5)
    Certification of release from indenture.
  - Account with James Scott, 1764? August 27; 1p.; Hunter, Samuel (Box 5)
    Lists items purchased, and balance due.
  - Bill of sale of knives and forks to Joseph Shippen, 1765 January 22; 1p.; Woodham & Young (Box 5)
    Philadelphia. Invoice for purchase.
  - Bill of Sale to James Burd for coffee, 1765 March 6; 1p.; Willing & Morris (Box 5)
    Philadelphia, Invoice for purchase.
  - Account of John Waid, 1765 March 26; 2pp.; Overseers of the Poor for Lancaster (Box 5)
    For Leacock Township, expenses incurred while providing for Thomas Moore.
  - Statement of accounts to Edward Lee, 1765 April 4; 1p.; Heirs of Samuel Simpson (Box 5)
    Note of expenses.
  - Advertisement of a horse, 1765 June 19; 1p.; Hutchenson, Thomas (Box 5)
    Notice of a stray horse.
  - Identification of a servant, 1765 October 4; 1p.; Simone, Adam, William Hamilton, and James Burd (Box 5)
    Relates to servants brought from Belfast Ireland to New Castle, PA.
  - Report of the overseers of the poor of Paxton, 1766 March 25; 1p. (Box 5)
    Accouting of money paid and due the overseers.
  - Order to John Steward to pay James Burd, 1766 May 4; 1p.; Stone, Christian (Box 5)
    Notice of payment.
  - Concerning bond for Craft Coss, 1766 August 14; 1p.; Burd, James (Box 5)
    Bond regarding Coss after his attack on his wife and threat to kill her.
  - Promissory note copy for £8.2.6, 1766 October 8; 1p.; Donachy, Patrick and Robert Sempell (Box 5)
    Note of payment to the estate of James Dunlap.
  - Robert McKee's account [with James Burd?] for weaving, 1766-1771; 1p. (Box 5)
    Lists amount of items, and cost.
  - Account of Hugh Swan, 1767 June 30; 1p.; McCormick, Dennis (Box OS)
    Sworn to before James Burd.
  - Summons to Hugh Swan..., 1767 October 8; 2pp.; Burd, James (Box 5)
    Summons to hear a plea of debt. On verso note of outcome.
  - Summons to Moses Campbell..., 1767 October 16; 2pp.; Burd, Jamse (Box 5)
  - Promissory note to James Burd, 1766 October 28; 1p.; Stewart, John (Box 5)
    Note of payment, reason unspecified.
  - Oath pertaining to boundary of land owned by the late William Cochrane, sworn to before James Burd, 1766 December 24; 1p.; Willson, Joseph (Box 5)
    Regarding the claim of James Wallace to part of William Cochrane's property.
  - Summons to Samuel Hook, 1767 June 29; 2pp.; Burd, James (Box 5)
    Summons for lack of payment in case against Thomas McKnight, where Hook was the bail. On verso note of Hook appearing on July 4.
  - Summons to Edward King..., 1767 July 18; 2pp.; Burd, James (Box 5)
    Summons to hear a debt plea. On verso note of the parties appearing.
  - Certification that Joseph Wilson has lived as their neighbor for years, 1767 December 2; 1p.; Cowden, Matthew, et al. (Box 5)
    Note that no dispute over lands exists with neighbors.
  - Statement concerning account of Isaac Davis, 1768 March 10; 1p.; Ramsour, Adam (Box 5)
    Regarding debt owed to him, noted before the Chester County justice.
  - Accounts..., 1768 April - May; 1p.; Armstrong, Robert (Box 5)
    Listing of purchases or services, and cost.
  - Promissory note to Dennis McCormick, 1768 June 6; 2pp.; Swan, Hugh (Box 5)
    Promise to pay stated amount, note on verso requesting payment.
  - Memorandum concerning the sale of a servant girl, 1768 July 2; 1p.; Patton, Robert (Box 6)
    Not to sell girl back to Mr. Harris if proper.
  - Certification that he baptized James Glancy, 1768 August 14; 1p.; Thomson, William (Box 6)
    Notice that he baptized a child, and the mother gave the father's name as Glancy.
  - Account of flour sold several different persons, 1768 August 18; 1p.; Burd, James (Box 6)
    Lists name, amount purchased, and cost.
  - Oath before Michael Swoope that his accounts for harness are correct, 1768 December 13; 1p.; Updefraff, John (Box 6)
    Affidavit that account against named individuals are true.
  - Affidavit that John Rutter owes him three shillings, 1769 February 11; 1p.; Fisher, Samuel (Box 6)
    Statement that Fisher appeared before James Burd and swore that Rutter owes him for smith work.
  - Promissory note to Robert Armstrong, Jr., 1769 March 13; 1p.; Lee Edward (Box 6)
    Promise to pay specified amount.
  - Oath that William Black owes for a gun, etc., 1769August 11; 1p.; King, Robert (Box 6)
    Affidavit that outstanding balance is ture.
    Unlocated 3/2011
  - Statement of accounts for purchase of wheat, to James Burd, 1769 September 10; 1p.; Rennick, Thomas (Box 6)
    Invoice for wheat.
  - Bill for salt to James Wallace, 1769 October 12; 1p.; Cox, Cornelius (Box 6)
    Bill stating amount purchased and cost.
  - Settlement of a disputed account, 1769 December 22; 1p.; Murray, James and John Bell (Box 6)
    Statement of outcome and cost.
  - Oath that James Hemphill owes for breeches, etc., 1770 April 16; 1p.; McConnel, William (Box 6)
    Affidavit that debt owed is valid.
  - Order of the Orphan's Court, 1770 June 12; 1p.; Shippen, Edward (Box 6)
    Order for past guardians to pay current guardians of Moses and George Dickey.
  - Account with James Burd for linen, 1771 May 11; 1p.; Lawman, Ludwick (Box 6)
    Lists number of items purchased and cost.
  - Report of auditors to James Burd..., 1771 December 16; 1p.; Holmes, Samuel (Box 6)
    Audit in the case of Philip Shawkin, defendant. Plantiff not named.
  - Statement of accounts to Aquilla Richards for cider, 1772 March 16; 1p.; Hendricks, Tobias (Box 6)
    Affidavit that outstanding accoutn against Richards is valid.
  - Deposition..., 1772 April 7; 1p. [fragments missing]; Hutcheson, Thomas (Box 6)
    Regarding case agains John Lytle.
  - Report of auditors to James Burd, 1772 April 15; 1p.; Postlethwait, John et al. (Box 6)
    Report regarding the accounts of Thomas McCormick and George Leadley.
  - Account with Mrs. McCormick, 1772 May - August; 1p.; Boyd, Robert (Box 6)
    Billing for medical services.
  - Certification of Hugh Cunningham's land, to James Burd, 1772 June 23; 1p.; Renick, Thomas, et al. (Box 6)
    Certification of land ownership.
  - Promissory note to Jacob Vator..., 1772 August 19; 1p.; McCallister, Eneas (Box 6)
    Boiler plate promissory note.
  - Proven account of Sameul Cummings, 1772 September 3; 1p.; Burd, James (Box 6)
    Billing for sundry goods.
  - Deposition before Edward Shippen, 1772 September 26; 1p.; Atlee, William (Box 6)
    Deposition regarding payment dispute between William Bell and Andrew Keiss.
  - Account with Josiah Rutton for schooling, ribbon, etc., 1773 February 16 - 1774 January 4; 3pp. [fragment missing]; Hutchinson, John (Box 6)
    Listing of accounts and services.
  - Account with Thomas Freby, 1773 October 24; 1p.; Lightfoot, Benjamin (Box 6)
    Listing of items purchased and cost.
  - Bill of sale of sugar, coffee and rum to James, 1773 November 6; 1p.; E. & A.Wickersham (Box 6)
    Lists items purchased and cost.
  - Affaidavit of Catherine Smith to John and Randle Mitchell, 1773 December 22; 1p.; Williams, John (Box 6)
    Statement that amount due is valid.
  - Account of Molly Hanakoogher for "Callico.", 1774 March 4; 1p.; Burd, James (Box 6)
  - Billof sale of rum, etc. to James Burd, 1774 July 8; 1p.; Forbes & Patton (Box 6)
    Lists of items purchased and cost.
  - Bill of sale to James Bird [sic] for sugar, coffee, and soap, 1774 July 14; 1p.; Forbes & Patton (Box 6)
  - to James Burd, Account for tea, 1774 August 10; 1p.; Forbes & Patton (Box 6)
    Lists of items purchased and cost, note regarding lack of loaf sugar.
  - Account with James Burd for linen, silk.., 1774 September 7; 1p.; Forbes & Patton (Box 6)
  - Bail for Philip Bottomer..., 1774 October 26; 1p.; Gross, Abraham (Box 6)
    Request to be entered as bail for Philip Bottomer.
  - Affidavit of Frederick Everhard, et al..., 1774 December 6; 1p.; Burd, James (Box 6)
    Statement regarding land agreement between Frederick Everhard and Adam Cleme.
  - Certificate pertaining to Stophell Shoop's land, 1775 April 17; 1p.; Dickey, William, et al. (Box 6)
    Statement regarding ownership of land.
  - Statement against Samuel Simson for debt., 1775 May 27; 1p.; Willis, William (Box 6)
    Statement of debt from Samuel and William Simson.
  - Gift of his rights in the account of John Cramer, to his father, Jacob Hyman, 1775 November 1; 1p.; Hyman, Christley (Box 6)
    Statement regarding transfer of account..
  - Statement of James Burd for breeches..., 1775; 1p.; Estate of Philip Deane (Box 6)
  - Statement of accounts with Capt. Bird [sic] for work..., 1775; 1p.; Tomb, George (Box 6)
    Lists items purchased, number, and cost.
  - Certification of indentured servants, 1779 December 5; 1p. [fragment missing]; Gibson, John (Box 6)
    Relates to the indenture of Philip Byrne.
  - Bill of payment for the School House, 1785 January 25; 2pp.; Moore, Henry (Box 6)
    Bill of payment for school house, and the deed.
  - Poem to Mr. John Yates: "Absurdity in Literature", 1786 September 2; 2pp. (Box 6)
    Poem. On verso account for John Jameson, July 20, 1760.
  - Account of James Burd, 1788 June 27; 1p.; McCormick, George (Box 6)
    Statement for sugar, nails, and coffee.
  - Bill of sale to James Burd, 1788 September 22; 1p.; Riddles, George (Box 6)
    For sugar and tea.
  - Account with Hugh Curry, 1788; 1p.; Burd, James (Box 6)
    For wheat, rye, etc.
  - Account with James Burd, 1791 September 28; 1p.; Crabb, William (Box 6)
    Bill for room and board.
  - Appraisal of a stray mare, September 14; 1p.; Welch, James, Robert Dick. (Box 6)
    Description and appraisal ordered of James Burd.
  - Assessment of Darby Township, n.d.; 1p. (Box 6)
    Tax assessment of inhabitants.
  - Assessments of Marple, Newton, and Haverford Townships, 2pp. (Box 6)
  - Assessments of Radnor, Upper Providence, and Nether Providence Townships, 2pp. (Box 6)
    Tax assessment of inhabitants..
  - Assessments of Ridley and Springfield Townships, 1p. (Box 6)
  - Account of James Burd, February; 1p. [fragments missing]; Sterling, Walter (Drawer Oversize)
    London. Insurance received on the Sea Hen.
  - Account of rum in the King's Stores..., n.d.; 1p. (Box 6)
    Gives name of person to be paid, amount of rum, and value.
  - Account with Philip Killion, n.d.; 1p.; Burd, James (Box 6)
    For britches and other clothing items.
  - Account of the freight of wine on the snow, Sally, n.d.; 1p.; Burd, James (Box 6)
    Lists amount of wine shipped and by whom.
  - Account with James Burd, n.d.; 1p.; Cox, William (Box 6)
    For various sums of money.
  - Account with various persons, n.d.; 1p.; Burd, Sarah Shippen, 1731-1784 (Box 6)
    Lists persons paid, and amount.
  - Statement of accounts with Capt.Hunter, n.d.; 1p.; Burd, James (Box 6)
  - Affidavit, n.d.; 1p.; Burd, James (Box 6)
    That sugar aboard the brig Beaver came from Jamaica.
  - Brewhouse account, n.d.; 1p.; Burd, James (Box 6)
    Paying for cooper, boards, etc.
  - Draft of sale to Michael Hoover, n.d.; 4pp.; Garber, Michael (Box 6)
    For lands in Lancaster County.
  - List of goods, n.d.; 2pp.; Burd, James (Box 6)
    Includes linens, nails, etc.
  - List of outstanding debts, 2pp. (Box 6)
    Gives name and amount of debt.
  - List of prices, current, n.d.; 1p. (Box 6)
    Prices for flour, bread, coffee, etc.
  - Memorandum of receipts..., 1p.; Burd, James (Box 6)
    From pocket memorandum book, gives notes of receipts.
  - Miscellaneous items, n.d.; 33pp. (Box 6)
    Fragments of letters, invoices, and cover pages. The majority of items are undated, with a few dated cover pages.
  - Petition..., n.d.; 1p.; McRoy, William (Box 6)
    Writing is light, and hard to read.
  - to the King of Thomas and John Penn, 7pp.; Penn, Thomas and John (Box 6)
    Petition to have the Northern and Western limits of Pennsylvania defined.
  - Proposed rules for the Shippensburg Library Company, n.d.; 2pp. (Box 7)
    Draft of proposed rules.
- Military, 1748 - 1772, undated; Series III
  - Report of stores at Fort Hunter (fragment only), 1748; 1p.; Patterson, James (Box 7)
    Gives weight for beef and pork.
  - Accout book, Fort Augusta, 1755 May 4 - June 17, 1763; 16pp.; Burd, James (Box 7)
    Account book for purchases and salary paid at fort.
  - List of gentlemen who sent their horses to haul the King's cannons to Shippensburg, 1755 August 20; 1p.; Scott, Thomas (Box 7)
    List of 14 names.
  - Report of physical condition of men, 1755 October 27; 1p.; Wilhelm, Dr. (Box 7)
    List of men, and statement of their health.
  - Orders for cannon, wine, etc., 1756; 1p.; Clapham, William (Box 7)
    Genral list of material needed.
  - Morning and evening reports of the garrison at Fort Augusta, Pennsylvania, 1756 January 11 - 1756 Dec 31; 111pp. (Box 7)
    Individual slips of paper giving the number of men by rank, equipment, and prisoners on hand in the fort. Occassional reports list men by name.
  - Morning/evening reports of the garrison at Ft Augusta, 1757 Jan 1- 1757 Aug 28 (Box 7)
  - Morning/evening reports of the garrison at Ft Augusta, 1757 Sept 3 - 1757 Oct 16 (Box 7)
  - Morning/evening reports of the garrison at Ft Augusta, 1757 Oct 18 - undated (Box 7)
  - Report on a court martial, 1756 January 28; 1p.; Burd, James (Box 7)
    Report of court martial for Simon Martin. [section giving report missing].
  - Report of a court martial, 1756 May 18; 3pp. [fragments missing]; Shippen, Joseph (Box 7)
    Court martial report for Timothy Brennon.
  - Invoice of stores at Hunter's Fort., 1756 September 11; 1p. (Box 7)
    Invoice for provisions and supplies.
  - Report of guns, etc. ..., 1756 October 16; 1p.; Miles, Lt. (Box 7)
    fragment of garrison report giving guns available.
  - Note to the officer of the guard that certain soldiers are suspected of stealing rum., 1756 December 9; 1p.; Shippen, Joseph (Box 7)
    Fort Augusta. Name of soldiers confined.
  - List of the officers names at Fort Augusta, 1756 December 10; 1p. (Box 7)
    List of rank and last name.
  - report of the guns at "foart agusta", 1756 December 12 - 1757 January 28; 15pp.; Kenney, Patrick (Box 7)
    Reports of guns at the fort on specific dates.
  - Grounds for arresting John Fields and Caspar Heiss..., 1756 December 25; 1p.; Shippen, Joseph (Box 7)
    Short note gifing reasons for each mans arrest.
  - List of stores at Fort Hunter, 1757 April 17; 1p.; Glabreath, Bartholomew (Box 7)
    List of provisions.
  - State of the Garrison at Fort Augusta, 1757 April 22; 2pp. (Box 7)
    Lists number of men per company at the fort.
  - Discharge to James Bambridge, 1757 May 10; 1p.; Burd, James (Box 7)
    Signed discharge.
  - Monthly report of the Garrison of ... in Fort Halifax., 1757 July 1; 1p. (Box 7)
    List of men by rank at the fort.
  - Affidavit in support of James Crampton's pettion..., 1757 July 15; 1p.; Gowdy, Samuel (Box 7)
    Lancaster. Statement regarding agreement between three soldiers.
  - Return of detachments from Col. Wyser's [sic] regiment., 1757 September 1; 1p.; Clayton, Asher (Box 7)
    List of officers and number of men at Fort Augusta.
  - Return of provisions at Camp Monongahela, 1757 October 29; 1p.; Forster, William (Box 7)
    Provisions on hand.
  - Waste book (in dreadful fragmentary condition), 1757; 47pp.; Burd, James (Box 7)
    Account book, quarter of which is missing.
  - A List of artillery, etc. at Fort Augusta, to James Burd, 1757; 1p.; Henry, Adam (Box 7)
    List of artillery and othe weapons at fort.
  - Account with James Burd for keeping his horses, 1758 January 18; 1p.; Whitebread, William (Box 7)
  - List of Capt. Jacob Morgan's Company ..., 1758 January 29; 1p. [fragments missing] (Box 7)
    Numbered list giving the names of men in company.
  - Certification of correctness of account of Jacob Hollman and John Serby for delivery of goods to Capt. Weiser: used by James Burd, 1758 March 6; 1p.; Basse, Christian (Box 7)
    Account inventory.
  - Report of sick..., 1758 April 30; 1p.; Morgan, John Surgeon (Box 7)
    Fort Augusta sick list by company.
  - Report of provisions at Fort Augusta, to James Burd, 1758 May 23; 1p.; Hunter, Samuel (Box 7)
    List of provisions, clothing, ammunition, and tools at Fort.
  - Report of men fit for service in James Burd's company, 1758 June 4; 1p. (Box 7)
    Gives number per company.
  - Invoice of provisions, 1758 August 30; 1p. (Box 7)
    List of items in the camp at the Clearfield.
  - Return of provisions, 1758 September 8; 1p.; Winston, Richard (Box 7)
    Stores at Loyalhanna.
  - Return of provisions, 1758 September 19; 1p.; Donnellon, Thomas (Box 7)
  - Account of horses, 1758 September 19; 1p.; Hunter, Samuel (Box 7)
    Horses received from various units..
  - Return of provisions, 1758 September 20; 1p.; Donnellon, Thomas (Box 7)
    Inventory of supplies.
  - Report to James Burd, 1758 October 2; 1p.; Johnston, Robert, et al. (Box 7)
    Report on beef, unfit to eat.
  - List of tools not returned, addressed to James Burd, 1758 October 10; 1p.; Lyon, William (Box 7)
    Tools not returned by Capt. Field's company.
  - Report on horses ..., 1758 October 14; 1p.; Hay, James (Box 7)
    Report from a reconnoitering party.
  - Petition to General Forbes, 1758 November 15; 1p.; Gillespie, Allan (Box 7)
    Request from a suttler to return to Raystown to obtain additional provisions to supply the Army.
  - Return of provisions in store at Loyalhannon., 1758 November 24; 1p. (Box 7)
  - Report of men, 1758 November 27; 1p.; Hydeler, Martin (Box 7)
    Report of detachments from the Royal Regiment of Artillery..
  - Return, 1758 November 28; 1p.; Hoops, Adam (Box 7)
    Provisions in store.
  - Fragment of a diary at a fort in western Pennsylvania, 1758 November; 4pp. (Box 7)
    Part of a diary, with fragments missing..
  - General hospital returns..., 1758 December 5; 1p.; Heinsman, Henry, Surgeon (Box 7)
    Patients listed by regiment or occupation..
  - Order for "flower" and whiskey., 1758; 1p.; St. Clair, John (Box 7)
    Order to get flour and whiskey from wagon.
  - Declaration of Martin Discentio, 1758; 1p. [fragments missing] (Box 7)
    A soldier of Capt. DuVitiers [i.e., deVitri or Charles Aubry] tells of Fort Duquesnes and departure of French officers and 300 Indians for attack on English [under James Burd] near Loyalhanna, October 12, 1758. Freeman and Smith 1372.
  - Tally of rations to James Burd (?), 1758; 1p. (Box 7)
    Lists weight of bulls, and the tally of rations sent to troops.
  - Inventory of goods, 1758; 1p.; Anderson, Robert (Box 7)
    Provisions belonging to the crown includes oats, and whiskey.
  - Master roll of men ..., 1758 January; 1p.; Wetterholt, John Nicholas (Drawer Oversize)
    List giving soldiers' name, enlistment date, county, age, and other traits.
  - Order on Golden and Moore for money., 1759 January 3; 1p.; Paris, Richard (Box 7)
  - Return of the detachment, 1759 April 21; 1p.; Morgan, Jacob (Box 7)
    Return for Second Battalion at Fort Ligonex.
  - Account for enlisting recruits, 1759 May; 1p.; Jameson, David (Box 7)
    Lists expenses paid for various aspects of enlistment.
  - Return of provisions at Fort Lytleton, 1759 June 1; 1p.; Graydon, Caleb (Box 7)
    List of provisions in store.
  - Passroll of recruits to William Hadden, 1759 June 8; 1p.; Burd, James (Box 7)
    Lists name, enlistment date, age, height, trade, birthplace, and complexion.
  - Pass list of men to work [on the road to Ohio?], 1759 June 12; 1p. (Box 7)
    Lists name, age, enlistment date, birthplace, and trade.
  - Pass roll of recruits to Capt. Maittars, 1759 June 15; 1p.; Burd, James (Box 7)
    Lists name, enlistment date, age, height, birthplace, and trade.
  - Pass roll of recruits for Capt. Samuel Poselwhite, 1759 June 15; 1p.; Burd, James (Box 7)
  - Recruiting account, 1759 June 19; 1p. [fragments missing]; Humphreys, Samuel (Box 7)
    Gives partial information on men and money paid them.
  - Marching orders of Henry Bouquet to Samuel Poselwait, 1759 June 24; 2pp.; Burd, James (Box 7)
    Orders to march command to Sadsbery and Martich (?) Townships in Lancaster County to help with wagons.
  - Report on Peter Daugherty, 1759 June 25; 1p.; Armstrong, C. (Box 7)
    Finds fit for service.
  - Account with William Smith..., 1759 June - 1760 February; 1p.; Burd, James (Box 7)